timebridge.com 2009-06-29

# Free Calendar Software & Scheduling Tool | TimeBridge - Privacy Policy

Last Updated: August 14, 2007 

We here at TimeBridge Inc. (“TimeBridge”) know it is important that you understand how information about you is used and shared. We provide this Privacy Policy to explain our policies and procedures for the collection, use and disclosure of information received from users of our website [www.TimeBridge.com](http://www.timebridge.com/) (the "Site") and the TimeBridge software downloaded from the Site ("Software") (collectively the "Services"). 

If you have any questions or comments about our practices or this Privacy Policy please contact us at [privacy@timebridge.com](mailto:privacy@timebridge.com)

  * This Privacy Policy applies only to the Services and is incorporated into the TimeBridge Terms of Service Agreement. 
  * We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of material changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. Please consult the Site regularly for changes. Unless otherwise defined in this policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the meanings provided in the TimeBridge Terms of Service Agreement. 
  * By using our Services you are consenting to TimeBridge processing your information as described in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. These uses include the collection, storage and deletion, disclosure and transfer of your information to and from the United States to provide you with the Services you have requested. 

#####  Information Collection and Use 

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our Services and its features, to administer your account and to enable users to enjoy and easily navigate the Site. 

Personal Information: 

  * When you register with the Site and/or download the TimeBridge software (“Members”) or merely reply to a Member’s invitation to participate in a meeting without registering with us (“Non-Members”) (collectively referred to as “Participants”) we may collect personally identifiable information, including, but not limited to, name, email address, postal address, telephone number, credit card number, and account user name and password (“Personal Information”). Personal Information is information about you that when on its own or in combination with other identifiers can be used to contact or identify you. We use your Personal Information to provide you the Services, facilitate your use of the Site and respond to your inquiries. 
  * We also may collect (i) any non-personally identifiable information that is provided to TimeBridge as part of registration or in a Participant’s response to an invitation, including, but not limited to, time zone; what email client a Participant uses (e.g., Outlook), and job function; and (ii)non-personally identifiable service usage data, including, but not limited to, whether a Non-Member ultimately registers to become a Member, the volume of the Meeting Materials (defined below) Participants circulate amongst themselves as a result of using the Services and the number of meetings TimeBridge Users schedule through use of the Services (collectively “Anonymous Demographic Information”). We may combine your Personal Information with this Anonymous Demographic Information or with aggregate information collected from other Participants to attempt to provide you with a better experience and improve the quality and value of the Services. From time to time, the use of Anonymous Demographic Information and Personal Information will include providing you with targeted advertising as you use the Services such that you can have access to information and products that may be of interest to you. 
  * As a Participant or a Site visitor just browsing (who has provided us with their email address) we may use your Personal Information to send you via email TimeBridge newsletters, promotional materials about other products or services and other information that you have requested or that may be of interest to you. We may also email you messages that allow you to purchase new or enhanced TimeBridge products and services. Where Participants agree to the terms and conditions of TimeBridge Terms of Service they are given the opportunity to opt-in to the receipt of such information from us in the future. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such information from us, you may follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in the communication or you may also update your registration preferences information. (See “Changing or Deleting Information,” below.) 

Log Information. When you visit the Site, whether as a Participant or a Site visitor just browsing, like many websites our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website (“Log Information”). This Log Information may include information such as your IP address, date and time, browser type and the domain from which you are visiting. For most users accessing the Internet from an Internet service provider (or “ISP”), the IP address will be different every time you log on. We do not use this information to identify you personally. We use it to analyze usage trends, administer the Site and the Service and for the Site’s technical maintenance. 

#####  Cookies 

Like many websites, we use “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies for two purposes. First, we utilize persistent cookies to save your registration account user name and password for future logins to the Services. Second, we utilize session ID cookies to enable certain features of the Services, to better understand how you interact with the Services, and to monitor aggregate usage of the Services by Participants and web traffic routing on the Site. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted from your computer when you disconnect from the Services. Third party advertisers on the Site may also place or read cookies on your browser. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Site or all functionality of the Services. You can learn more about the use of cookies by visiting [http://networkadvertising.org ](http://networkadvertising.org/) or <http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie> . 

#####  Phishing 

We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, your TimeBridge user name, login password, or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication. 

Identity theft and the practice currently known as "phishing" are of great concern to TimeBridge. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is our priority. For more information about phishing, you may want to visit the Federal Trade Commission’s website at <http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/edu/pubs/consumer/alerts/alt127.htm>

#####  Information Sharing and Disclosure 

Participants. Participants have the opportunity to share various types of information amongst themselves through use of the Services. You can upload and post meeting agendas, your bio and other documents (“Meeting Materials”) you wish to have accessible to meeting Participants on a designated web meeting space. This content along with all other information related to your use of the Services, including, but not limited to, meeting times, meeting occurrences and discussion board information is stored and maintained on TimeBridge’s secure servers. Providing your Personal Information and any other information about you via the Services, is voluntary and this information will be visible to other Participants and should correlate with the degree of interaction you want to have with other Participants. 

Anonymous Information. We may share Anonymous Demographic Information and Log Data with third parties for industry analysis and demographic profiling. This information will not contain your Personal Information. 

Service Providers. We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Services, to provide the Services on our behalf or to perform Site-related services (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, hosting services, database management and improvement of the Site's features). These third parties may have access to your Personal Information, but only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to use it for any other purpose.

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement. TimeBridge cooperates with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of TimeBridge or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity. 

Business Transfers. TimeBridge may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including information provided by you, in connection with a merger, reorganization, or sale of assets, or in the event of bankruptcy. If TimeBridge becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

#####  Changing or Deleting Your Information 

All Members may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information in their registration profile. Non-Members may also request deletion of their Personal Information from our servers. If Participants completely delete any such information, their use of the Services may be limited or terminated. If you would like us to delete your records in our system, please contact us and we will attempt to accommodate your request. See below for privacy contact information. 

#####  Data Retention 

We reserve the right to retain your Personal Information or other data collected from you as a result of your use of the Services to prevent fraud and misuse of the Services. 

#####  Security & International Transfer 

TimeBridge is very concerned with safeguarding your information. We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access. Your information may be transferred to and maintained on computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. TimeBridge transfers Personal Information to the United States and maintains and processes it there. You consent to such transfer. 

#####  Links to Other Sites 

Our Site may contain links to other websites. If you choose to visit an advertiser by "clicking on" a banner ad or other type of advertisement, you will be directed to that third party’s website. The fact that we link to a website or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. This Privacy Policy addresses the use and disclosure of information that we collect from you through this Site. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit. 

#####  Our Policy Toward Children 

This Site is not directed to children under 18. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [privacy@timebridge.com](mailto:privacy@timebridge.com). If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files. 

#####  Contacting Us 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@timebridge.com](mailto:privacy@timebridge.com) or at: 

TimeBridge, Inc. 

c/o Privacy Officer 

840 Battery, Second Floor 

San Francisco, CA 94111 

(c) 2006 TimeBridge, Inc. All rights reserved.
